If you collect garbage, you'll have
garbage in implementation stage. I feel
like the moment when for example they
not developing they implementing the
buying services and then just think
about it how you going to use it and
again talk to legal team to understand
what would be the risks because there is
some regulation even saying that there
is prohibited AI activities you need to
be aware of. So that implementation your
use case can be very tricky and very
harmful for your organization. So why do
not just go over those list of high-risk
activities talk to legal team and
understand in early stage what you can
do with those tool and what you cannot.
So if you still have a problem you're
trying to solve with AI and it's better
to understand in early stage.
Andre welcome to the signal room. It's
great to have you. Oh, thank you, Chris.
Thank you for having me here. I'm so
excited to do this conversation. Yeah,
I'm happy to be here.
It's been a little bit, but you know, I
think we met out in Las Vegas at the put
data first conference, right?
Yeah, that correct. I love all events in
person. And you can you can meet uh
experts and just just talk about
different expertise because that one was
basically mostly about security data put
data first but also I met couple privacy
experts and of course everyone were
talking about AI implication and how it
how it works together with privacy
security and all related data of course
data
that was good that was one of the things
that kind of struck me about it because
I've been to conferences and you know AI
is certainly a topic, but it was really
cool for me because the biggest concerns
that people are talking about these days
are really around governance and and the
healthc care sector in particular. We're
we're a little behind the behind the the
curve on that one. A lot of folks like
yourselves were like really talking
about this stuff with a lot of passion
and you know for me it was like very
very comforting to know that people like
you are really engaged in and thinking
about the security the privacy aspects
of it and kind of how pushing us a bit
on on that side of it so that we are
very thoughtful about how we use it.
It's one thing to have good intention.
It's it's another thing to right. So
very excited about having our
conversation this morning. Let's kind of
start on you know the real basic
premises that that people don't probably
understand very well. Can try to explain
for so that the role of privacy and AI
governance as a manager or to a manager
that's not an expert. Yeah, great
question because few years ago we just
had kind of privacy governance right
data governance but then new topic came
AI and now we there is some demand on
experts about privacy and AI governance
because both of them touch data data
touch all the industries and as a
manager for me most important is to of
course to support business uh on
achieving their goals. They want to
build new AI tools or implement buying
uh some services from third parties,
vendors and those initiatives now just
going so fast and role of privacy and
air governance experts is to keep up and
also be proactive. How you can be
proactive? You need to think ahead a
little bit and of course build processes
and controls in place. I don't want to
scare people with word controls because
controls means you can go with your
initiative business initiative when you
have those controls if it's required and
you can feel safe if you implement those
things up front. What we call privacy by
design. Yeah. implement uh some
processes, controls, policies on time in
early stage and then you can just be
sure that when you when you're launching
your product or feature, you already
done. And it's not just about complying
uh with requirements which is very
important but also it's about building
trust with with clients and be
transparent as much as you can because
when people start using new tools they
definitely
uh the first concern they have what will
happen with their data once they enter
to the service or even touch website
right and say uh again they non-experts
Maybe I mean they known privacy known AI
governance experts. So they want to feel
safe and trust is something you need to
build. So role of privacy in AI
governance manager is to help business
to implement to build first of all to
understand what controls and processes
you need to have in place to make sure
that you using data in safe way. then
also following in ongoing base following
those controls and I I would say I would
highlight one more role of privacy
manager is to educate people on um
privacy and AI governance it's it's not
something that the main goal is to solve
problem it's mostly I would say it's
also about building building uh to be
proactive building trust with clients
and even using this like when you have
strong governance and privacy controls
in place as a business owner.
You mentioned governance and u the sense
of controls and I think that's one of
the the bad wraps that that governance
has had in times past but it it's now
not something that's intended to slow
you down. It's the only way you can
safely speed up. I mean that you know I
just was working on developing a website
and I do not code but the technologies
are so crazy. I built a pre-roll website
myself and I mean it's moving between
screens and all kinds of things. So I
can only imagine the the types of risks
that could be taken if people are
engaging, you know, someone like
yourself with this expertise to help
them understand where to put your guard
rails and don't do that and don't, you
know, get ahead of yourself cuz we're
going way too fast at this point.
Yeah, definitely. And those controls
like just simple example would be uh put
proper language language popup window
message that you interacting with the
system. For example, this is example of
controls. It's nothing scary. It just uh
try to design it as early as you can in
early stage of your product development
and you okay to go. So just something
that will help you and just as you're
saying it's not stopping that's why
that's why I feel like one of the role
of the manager to help people to kind of
change mind a little bit or shift to
kind of culture of privacy and AI governance.
Yeah. I mean that kind of know touches
on there areas that people are confusing
you know you know control versus
governance that's Warner but what are
some of the other ways that people might
be confused about really what this means
or what like some of the misconceptions
people might have about privacy and AI
governance
maybe I would highlight one misconcept
that governance it's something that
should be handled just by legal and
privacy team, but I feel like we really
encourage product people, marketing
teams, crossf functional teams to be
proactive and just to contribute as much
as I can to talk to our teams earlier so
we can discuss and again just even if
there is some risks another topic to
talk about risks when uh we saying risk
it can be mitigated again we can put
some controls in place and it doesn't
mean risk you should stop. Most likely
you can mitigate that. I feel like
privacy and governance it's work for all
cross functional teams. Yeah, I think
it's a it's an interesting challenge
too. Organizations are pretty
sophisticated and they've got a lot of
different verticals and there's going to
be some people you need in the room.
They don't really don't spend a lot of
time thinking about this kind of
technology, but we need them to because
their subject matter expertise really is
needs to be represented to make sure
that we are understanding all of the
areas that we could have risk. It's
important people understand that you're
not there to control things. You're
there to support them as a manager that
is responsible for this stuff. Um, and I
maybe I think I'm kind of cool because I
mean you've you've been pretty upbeat
all the time that we've spoken about
this. Maybe you could talk a little bit
about an initiative that you're that
you're working on that excites you. I
mean, I don't know if people think about
privacy and security and governance and
think that might be exciting, but I kind
of think it is because you've been we've
been having a fun conversation since we
met.
Yeah. I feel like privacy and AI
governance now sometimes associates as
something very complicated for
non-experts and even for privacy experts
even for legal teams. It's uh
overwhelmed with new regulations with
complicated topics. So I feel like one
of the initiatives that excites me is to
implement educational trainings to talk
to um non-experts cross functional teams
about simple things fundamental things
what is what is personal data how AI
even related to personal data so what is
the main principles of uh handling
personal data I mean I feel like I can
talk even just about one principle data
minim optimization. I can I need one day
to talk about data minimization that
teams you you cannot collect data just
in case. Right. Right. You need to you
need to you need to know why you that
data and most important you need to
explain your customers and uh get their
consent that how you going to use that
data. So it just you save a lot of time
and maybe f and maybe save time when you
need to do future assessments when you
talk to your cross cross functional
teams just now yeah set up 15 minutes I
don't think like you need couple hours
meetings every day talking about privacy
just 15 minutes about privacy uh maybe
once a week or something like that it
should be very simple conversation about
most important important things and that
shift that education not happening
overnight
it just takes time so that efforts
really require and I like implementing
trainings also I'm very excited about
automation because again it's about
simplifying privacy processes when you
can implement tool that help you to uh
automate and move from Excel sheets to
um traceable uh workflow, sending
notifications in assessments, setting up
tasks involve people through one tool to
collaborate on data privacy and AI
governance. There is a lot of
similarities how you handle data privacy
and governance process. So, uh yeah,
these two things I I feel like it's very
important to keep in mind for for
privacy experts. You you you mentioned
something that I think is really uh
worth kind of pausing on for a second.
Historically,
in my experience over the years, you
know, people that are dealing with data
and analytics, data warehousing, they
tend to go for I want to pull in
everything. I I just want to, you know,
have you talk about that just for a
second because this is a shift that has
to be made and organizations have to
think about this differently now because
if they're going to start using the AI
capabilities on it, now you have to
really think about things different.
that you you can't just have these these
uh these new programs or solutions
attached to the ocean and think
everything's going to be okay. Uh that
there's got to be some some uh
conversations and and ways to handle
this. And if I know we didn't talk about
this previously, but maybe just talk a
little bit about how you you support
teams and help them to think through
that effort because it just seems like
it's a it's going to be a a pretty
significant shift in how they think and
how they manage the data sets. Yeah,
great question because I feel like now
every team wants to on board some tool
and most likely that tool will have a
high capabilities because it's speeding
up process and everything but I feel
like everything starts with simple
question why why you need that tool what
that tool will be doing for us and how I
mean as as a privacy side I would ask
how they going to use our data and
whether they we want them to permit to
use that data. Is this mandatory
mandatory or we can turn it off,
right? So it's it's just a simple
conversation with business owner of the
process or who is going to to implement
that initiative just to to talk about
what is the value of the tool and is it
really solving our problem issues or
challenges and okay now let's talk about
data and do we have controls in place
for that if not can we implement that
quickly in parallel with your uh with
your initiative
Are there any risks? Are there any high
risks? And whether there is a way to
mitigate it and again talking about
risks, it just something we need to work
on. Of course, if there is high risk and
there is no mitigation, there is might
be question to stop that initiative.
It's a it's a conversation with business
in early stage.
Yeah. And I think you know you're you're
touching on probably one of the more
important aspects of the governance
piece of this. It's really what
responsible and ethical AI and talk a
little bit about that. What and how
would you describe that in your words?
What does it really mean? I feel like we
touched a little bit this topic but
ethical AI there are many subtopics sub
things to talk about but I wouldn't
highlight this one that to be very
transparent
and with your clients customers and even
if it's not requirement think about what
you can disclosure on your website to
put more information for customers so
they aware about your technologies is if
you have AI component maybe you can
explain the logic logic behind AI. So
how much you are are you transparent
with your customers about your business
and whether you have controls in place
let them know let them know what
certification you have. Are you
following the major certifications?
Do you kind of how you care about data
and AI safe use in your business and
just make that publicly available so
people can go read people reading now
people reading more I'm sure and they
want to know about your business and AI
component because there is different
opinion about safe use right use of your
data what AI can do and how scalable
abilities and like then they make
decision do I need to use this tool or
not
touching you're touching on another
great
an important topic you mentioned the
explanability piece of it there's a
translation needed because you you're
not going to as a hobbyist understand
you know it's not like you can turn over
the code and someone's going to be able
to understand what you're doing with it
there's really a translation aspect of
it so I mean how do you think about
translating abstract principles into
concrete controls.
Yeah, I feel like first of all you'll be
translating that to different audiences.
For example, your employees who have
some expertise, right? They they they
have expertise in tech most likely about
data in general, not just personal data
but in data. So you can talk to your
teams just help them to understand that
that transparency explanability is very
important and involve them to to create
those documentation about how it works
to help them to uh actually future
products because now they invol
understand importancy they not just
reading what you created you actually
working with you together to develop
this those controls. Another audience
would be just your visitors for example
on your website, your future customers
or current customers. So then you need
maybe to make sure that you're talking
to them same language I mean
professional language tech language and
explaining simple things to help them to
understand like in plain language in
simple language how your system works
and I feel like collaboration with legal
team would be very helpful because they
have component of regulation language
and they can explain to you and you and
ask all questions legal first and then
kind of translate that to make that more
accessible to to your audiences uh to
understand that everyone will benefit
from that.
Right. Yeah. I I think the the tendency
at least in the last year or so
everyone's going at such a breakneck
pace moving so fast. Um yeah, if you're
not involving the legal experts, you're
you're probably have risk right now that
you don't know about. And it's it's a
good idea to go go talk legal team. Get
get them involved. It it's just it's
just this really important thing we
don't we don't lose sight of right now
because I think this is going to be the
year of governance for sure. And I don't
think it's all going to be rosy. I think
it's going to be some some bumps here.
So I'd encourage people to to really
hear this this point and Andre's
absolutely right. You you want to work
with your legal team. There are all
kinds of different um reasons that that
things fail. Where do you see the
biggest current failure modes? Data
collection, model design, deployment,
organizational culture.
Great question because every piece is
important. you start maybe with data
collection and I feel like I'm not going
to say something new when I when I
mention that if you collect garbage
you'll have garbage about data. So yeah,
sorry about that terminology, but also I
want to
yeah I feel like in the in
implementation
stage I feel like I want to highlight
the moment when for example company they
not developing AI they they implementing
the buying services and then just think
about it how you going to use that tool
and um again talk to legal team to
understand what would be the risks
because some regulation even uh saying
that there is prohibited AI activities
you need to be aware of. So that
implementation you your use case can be
very tricky and very harmful for your
organization. So why do not just go over
those lists couple list of high-risk
activities or prohibited activities talk
to legal team and understand in early
stage what you can do with those tool
and what you cannot so if you still have
a problem you're trying to solve uh with
AI and it's better to to understand in
early stage maybe you need to look for
another vendor or implement controls
right start implementing right Now
because some controls really take place
to implement it's not happening
overnight and for example some
certification or registration your
system in database whatever it kind of I
it will take time so yeah I would say um
I don't know sometimes it's all comes to
communication and collaboration between
teams if product or business owner come
to privacy team AI governance and just
share ideas when it's in idea stage then
it's easier to manage. you're you're
hitting on I think something that we got
we really need to think think about a
little bit differently than we have
before inside of a company there's all
generally there's an intent to speak the
same language right so you and I have
talked a little bit about AI literacy
before but what does it mean what does
AI literacy mean for non-technical staff
versus technical staff I mean they
really do have to be able to communicate
and understand each other about that
it's it could be even worse than a
language barrier if it's not if it's not
given some attention
definitely and uh that AI literacy um I
mean there is different definitions but
I would say there is at least three
components the first of all it's about
AI and technical side how what is the
capabilities how it works and for
example what is their performance
indicators, what are their metrics you
can you can measure performance, what is
the accuracy, what are there other
technical things you you need to
understand logic behind AI. The second
component would be it's of course it's
regulation. You need to you need to know
like what you can do, what you cannot do
with AI and what controls need to be in
place. And we talked about this today a
lot. So you cannot you cannot avoid
governance piece. It's it's just
mandatory and also opportunity to to
scale your business and add to your
value proposition that oh my gosh we
have such good governance in place. So
we want to talk we want to give it as a
benefit to our to our clients. And third
component is ethical AI use. ethical
use. I feel like uh what we touched
today um you cannot collect data just in
case. So it's then what purpose you will
be using that data for and that ethical
um part now sounds more often and more
because it's about how people feel about
using the data and what how transparent
AI systems. So these three components so
since you mentioned technical stuff and
nontechnical things they both would
benefit because technical things is
requirement and technical personnel can
explain this site to for example for
privacy team hey you guys tech please
give us a little bit more information
how it works and non-technical stuff of
course we can we can talk to tech to
explain importancy of understanding
ending technical side. So just just
mutually beneficial things.
Now we've we've talked a little bit
about their data usage uh things here,
but let's talk about some of your your
lessons that you've learned leading
privacy awareness and training uh since
you've kind of opened this topic and how
these lessons apply to AI literacy.
Great question. It's a very very big
topic about trainings and I feel like uh
sometimes businesses need to shift to
kind of just to think about it that you
using so much data and you serving
customers.
So uh you have so much regulations, you
have so much governance in place. How
much time do you dedicate to educate
people on what you have? Right? just
compare like how much is it compared to
what you have and uh again education
happening not that quickly not overnight
and especially when people facing data
privacy training or governance first
time they they just it's like something
undiscovered yet much and something
unknown and that that's why maybe you
feel sometimes resistance from crossf
functional teams
uh another things I feel like now it's
almost responsibility of privacy experts
to make that materials privacy content
interesting to people then well then
good design come to play comes to play
because
uh you can think in different way how to
design your content your slides maybe
short videos and it is ongoing should be
an ongoing base
you know it's It's increasingly
important as the the regulatory
landscape seems to be evolving towards
explanability and transparency and at
the moment it's it's not really at the
federal level moving at the pace that it
is some some states. So, you know I you
know some of the first cases in
California in Texas for example they
they've put some things in place for
healthcare uh specifically uh that are
requiring the the transparency and and
the explanability in order to actually
achieve informed consent and there's you
know pending lawsuits about this stuff
now. So if if you're not designing with
that in mind, you you really need to
take another look at that. Uh so there
you you don't end up having to go and
pull something out of production and
rebuild it. But that's the risk you take
if you're not thinking about those
things. Uh 50 states in 50 different
approaches is quite possible. It's
happened before. So I just hash people
make sure that you're looking for that.
Yeah. And one more thing about sorry I'm
I'm just want to add one more thing to
this question. I pop up in my mind. Uh
sometime ago, I believe privacy
trainings were like something like
happening once a year or just on
boarding security privacy trainings and
I feel like sometimes there is a kind of
those trainings mostly about security
and less about data privacy.
So it's just naturally people forget
about data privacy. there is not huge
retention knowledge about data privacy.
So I feel like there is some shift
required from just on boarding trainings
to ongoing privacy and AI governance.
Similar similar similar challenge uh
educating people about governance AI
governance. It should be small small
pieces of information in ongoing base
well designed. Think about maybe involve
designers who will help you to uh again
cross functional collaboration who will
help you to design your content well and
think about it how deliver interesting
way
right yeah I think for there's got to be
a shift in thinking about this from the
standpoint of a AI models are evolving
and they're they're being retrained
constantly. So, you know, we you can't
really treat this as a checkbox like
like you we could probably do in some
instances in the past because the
policies just didn't change that much
because the the the outputs that the
organization's accustomed to really
don't change that much in terms of how
they're being produced. You know, if you
figure
most workflows don't change overnight
and they they never have, but today
that's not necessarily the case. So, I
think it's a really important uh concept
that you're talking about there cuz it's
got to be it's got to be thought of
differently and we've got to have some
kind of a a process to keep feeding uh
the information to make sure that we we
keep current and people are
understanding, you know, this stuff and
know they know what the risks are.
Yeah, that's that's that's a big topic
definitely.
What do you think are some of the common
misunderstandings that you encounter
like this AI is magic? Well, Leo will
handle it. Don't worry about that. Or
it's it's the vendor. They've got this.
What are some of the the things that you
run into?
I feel like I feel like Yeah, we talked
about this a little bit. Just just feels
like uh even if vendor saying everything
okay, you have everything. Just go over
again everything and involve your teams
and use that maybe as for educational
purposes. just do it again and make sure
that that what they saying works and uh
if you're planning to use that vendor
for long term just
uh go a little bit deeper and again
start with business owners involve
responsible people in the process
communicate with vendor and sometimes on
the way you can uncover something like
new cases business business have plans
to use use uh this tool in different use
cases and how you can know that without
collaboration how how legal or just
privacy tip can handle that if they do
not know business purposes or plans
about those tool or specific
implications. So yeah um we just
technically cannot handle uh data
privacy and a governance by ourself and
I feel like uh when you collaborating
with teams it just show that you have
great communication inside company with
other teams and that just also add to
your product value proposition that
everything clear even for non-experts
and when they talking to prospects facts
they can mention and sound like experts
about privacy or well educated people
about privacy well privacy it's very
often about data so it's I mean since
you have a lot of data most likely there
is some personal data and people want to
know about it why not to to add to your
expertise you're happy to share
we talk a lot about the you know the
technology and the data but maybe talk
let's talk a little bit about the the
the role that of tools and platforms
like one trust versus human process and
culture. That's an area that's I think
not getting quite enough airtime right
now. We're talking really it's the
cultural stuff that and the human
impacts. Um would love to hear your
thoughts about that. Yeah, it's a great
question and I feel like automation
similar to AI uh serving one purpose to
help to help to save time to simplify
some very predictable tasks
and so you can focus on more strategic
things. uh I love automation and
particularly I work in using and have
got certification for one trust so uh
it's very good practice and says about
your data handling maturity level how
you handle data so you have one tool one
source of truth about data for example
about vendors you have one profile of
vendor all risks all your communication
all uh mitigation measures you
implemented in one tool in one profile.
You can generate reports. You can you
can have dashboards to see how many
risks you have. What is the situation
overall situation about privacy in you?
uh it's very kind of hard a bit harder I
found harder to do with with without
tool and it's definitely save time and
even um non-privacy experts they can if
they have permission they can go to
specific vendor and take a look hey can
we work with this vendor do we want to
work in the future what is the risk
level how responsible they are to
mitigate those risks And it's just great
tool collaborate together on on data
privacy and AI governance. And just keep
in mind that tool like that you need to
most likely you will need to customize a
lot of things because every business
unique and to be looking for different
to to cover different goals. So once you
work on setting up the tool and
customize everything then you can really
enjoy uh flow workflow and automated
tasks and your assessments will be going
easier and just you will have visibility
what's going on with your privacy and
what situation you have there and AI
governance and you can share your
practices with your potential clients.
you can just uh generate reports or uh
share certification whatever. So it's
very convenient and I feel like it's
really says about great leadership
support about how you handle your data
AI governance. So things to consider I
would really encourage businesses to
have it some some data management tool
whatever you select. As we're kind of
getting towards the end of our time, uh
there's a couple of topics here that
they're they're really related, but it
occurs to me that there's probably some
some folks listening that are really not
quite sure how they're going to embed
governance into product and engineering
workflows. So, it doesn't feel like a
blocker. That's one side of it. But also
there's there's some skills that I think
are probably um ones that people should
be thinking about and prioritizing as
well. So maybe you can kind of talk
about those those two things. So you
know first how do you embed the
governance? Uh but then what are some of
the skills that you think need to be
developed or acquired if an organization
doesn't already have them? Yeah, I feel
like it's uh something that almost every
business will face this challenge how to
build governance. But there is one easy
component if you have privacy data
governance in place. You can you can
transition you can transfer many
controls from there to to AI governance.
For example, you can handle your
assessments
uh using some questions from your
previous questionnaers. uh you can use
same tool data management tool to handle
AI assessments
vendor assessments internal assessments
and talking about skills I feel like uh
it's very clear you need to have
technical things uh data privacy skills
like getting some certification from
famous organizations but also I feel
like we missing um in general it's kind
of not something People think about even
communication skills,
right?
Even project management skills, how to
how to communicate to cross functional
teams in early stage. How to embed
privacy component, AI governance
component to
project scope, project plan and uh how
to use project management tools to
create that visibility and communication
sharable documents,
dashboards and everything just to
simplify life for non-expert non-privacy
experts and help them to simplify
everything And uh yeah project
management skills will be very helpful
communication and communication would be
helpful for every team because we will
be talking and it's okay to talk
initiatives in the beginning giving
feedback I feel like communication
skills uh how to give feedback and
request feedback request help from
experts different fields it's it's all
about communication and it's not just
naturally you born with those skills.
There is skills you can learn a lot
about. Take some courses, take some um
education on that component also would
help because crossf functional uh
collaboration uh really will help to
save time and there's reduce those
blotters.
You lead into the
probably one of the biggest most
important points of of our conversation.
Where would you encourage people to who
are listening who want to learn more
where should they be looking or their
community certifications resources where
where would you point them? Sure. My
experience there is much more resources
you can learn from. I mean um I got
couple certificates from EIP
organization international organization
of privacy professionals and there is u
AI governance certification as well.
It's not just about privacy but they
have that also since we talked about
automation and implementing tools. I
think um one trust uh has a lot of
educational materials. You can find them
some of them free access uh and uh maybe
you can start from there. And also I I
personally like how much educational
materials you can find on different
platforms like linkadin or corsera or
like just just try to focus there is so
much so much information just try to
focus on what specific area you want to
work on right
and uh maybe you want to be security
experts it's a bit different from
privacy even we working closely but it's
it's funny because when I go to to just
conference. Sometimes I I I hear a
question hey what do you do and do
privacy and oh you security guy there is
some similarities but this is where we
need to start to educate people just to
for even from simple things what is the
security what is the privacy what data
you're responsible responsible for and u
I think this is kind of a great question
to people to understand even like okay
why AI system needs my data and where
like search where to go on business
website where to go specifically to read
like how that data is going to be used
so where is it where that component and
it's yeah it's it's just um I don't know
we talked today about a lot about
shifting to to that culture culture of
uh safe data and for businesses to
understand that can be your value part
of your value proposition
You can even
emphasize when you have good AI or
privacy and both governance in place.
Feel free to to add it to your value
proposition because it's working. Andre,
this has been a fantastic conversation.
I I've learned some things. Thank you.
Of course, I always enjoy speaking with
you uh for listeners. Uh you'll find uh
all kinds of good information in the
show notes. you'll you'll find the
anything you need to know about how to
reach out to Andre. If you have have
questions, you you just want to have a
conversation and and bit gleaned from
his wisdom a bit. I'm sure he he'd love
to hear from you. But that's going to do
it for this episode. And Andre, thank
you so much for being here. I can't
thank you enough. It's been fantastic.
Thank you, Curtis, so much for having me
here. And uh your questions just right
to the point. And I'm happy that uh you
curious about that and I'm sure our
audience want to know more about that
and of course uh there is experts from
different fields who really want to
become privacy experts and they want to
starts from somewhere and I'm sure they
will find implication of their expertise
in privacy field because it touchs a lot
and it's also a global and international
uh field where like privacy once
business have presence somewhere in
Europe or whatever it become become
international and global um global thing
and so so much things to learn about
privacy and now in governance so I'm
happy to share my knowledge uh with
people who want to reach out I'm happy
to talk to
excellent thank you so much
thank you Chris
that's it for this episode of the signal
room if today's conversation sparked
something in you an idea idea, a
challenge or perspective worth
amplifying, I'd love to hear from you.
Message me on LinkedIn or visit
cigarroompodcast.com
to explore being a guest on an upcoming
episode. Until next time, stay tuned,
stay curious, and stay human.